What do you think of when you hear the word ‘festival’?
当你听到“节日”这个词时会想到什么？
Is it music?
是音乐吗？
Maybe it’s film.
或许是电影？
Or could it be food?
又或者是美食？
Food festivals are a common occurrence in the UK and take place in all sorts of places and at all sorts of times: from Taste of London, in Regent’s Park each June to Aldeburgh Food Festival in Suffolk in September.
美食节在英国是常见的活动，它们在各种地点、不同时间举办：从每年六月摄政公园的“伦敦味道”美食节，到九月萨福克的奥尔德伯勒美食节。
Whatever your taste, there’s a food festival to match – no matter how specialised.
无论你的口味如何，总有一个美食节与之匹配——无论多么特别。
Are you a bit of a carnivore?
你是个食肉爱好者吗？
Then why not try Meatopia.
那么不妨试试“肉食乌托邦”美食节。
This three-day, London-based festival takes place at the end of August and is a meat lover's paradise.
这个在伦敦举办为期三天的美食节于八月底举行，是肉食爱好者的天堂。
In addition to a range of ethically sourced meat products, from juicy burgers to succulent steaks, attendees can listen to live music, watch butchery demos, and attend informal meat-based workshops.
除了许多来源符合伦理的肉类产品（比如动物被屠杀时较少痛苦），比如多汁的汉堡和牛排，参与者还能聆听现场音乐、观看屠宰演示，并参加非正规的肉类主题工作坊。
If you prefer a festival that will help you meet your five a day, then Vegfest is for you.
如果你更喜欢能帮助你达到每日五份蔬果摄入量的节日，那么“素食节”很适合你。
This vegan-friendly event takes place in a range of UK venues several times a year.
这个纯素食友好的活动每年在英国多处地点举办数次。
Here you can enjoy a wide selection of freshly prepared vegan food, learn culinary tips and hear talks on nutrition to help you make the most of your plant-based grub.
在这里，你可以享用花样繁多的现做纯素食，学习烹饪技巧，聆听关于营养的讲座，充分利用以植物为主的食物。
If that weren’t niche enough, what about a festival that is dedicated solely to marmalade?
如果这还不够小众，那么一个专门为橘子酱举办的节日如何？
Held in Cumbria, this tangy, zesty festival of preserves has been running for 13 years. It includes a competition to find the best homemade marmalade. There are thousands of entries from over 30 different countries across the globe.
这个在坎布里亚举办的味道浓烈的、热情洋溢的果酱节已举办了13年，其中包括评选最佳自制橘子酱的比赛，有来自全球30多个国家的数千份作品参赛。
If you’d prefer something with a little more kick to it, then you could attend The Ginger and Spice Festival held in Market Drayton.
如果你更喜欢带点刺激味道的活动，不妨参加德雷顿集市的“生姜与香料节”。
It celebrates its town’s historic connection to Robert Clive, who returned from India with ginger. Because of this, they specialise in baking gingerbread, but also sell a range of artisan spices from mild to hot.
该节日纪念小镇与从印度带回生姜的罗伯特・克莱夫的历史渊源，因此以烘焙姜饼为特色，也售卖从温和到辛辣的一系列手工香料。
If you have a sweet tooth, then it could be that the National Honey Show, which started in 1921 and is the largest event of its kind, is the place for you to be.
如果你爱吃甜食，那么始于1921年、同类活动中规模最大的“全国蜂蜜展”可能很适合你。
This three-day event attracts over 2000 entrants to their traditional competition, and offers lectures and workshops on beekeeping and, of course, that gooey, syrupy golden nectar, honey.
这个为期三天的活动吸引超2000名参赛者参加传统比赛，并提供讲座和工作坊，关于养蜂和蜂蜜，就是那黏糊糊、糖浆般的金色花蜜。
While there’s no accounting for taste, the UK has something to offer most people.
虽然口味因人而异，但英国总能满足大多数人的需求。
From large-scale festivities, to the smaller more amateur gatherings, one thing is certain: people are passionate about their food.
从大型庆典，到更小型的业余聚会，有一点毋庸置疑：人们对食物充满热情。
And while some of the products on offer might be an acquired taste, when food is given that much attention, it’s unlikely to leave a bad taste in anyone’s mouth.
尽管有些产品可能需要慢慢培养才能喜欢，但当食物被如此用心对待时，它不太可能让人失望。